winnersisland.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Scratch cards & Scratch games by WinnersIsland

At WinnersIsland.com we are committed to protecting and respecting our players personal information. We recognize the importance of protecting information collected from users and have created this Privacy Policy to let You know what information We collect, why We collect this information and how We use the collected information.

## 1\. Privacy

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of WinnersIsland’s End user license agreement and Our Terms And Conditions. By Clicking / Checking “I Agree” or access or use WinnersIsland website, You automatically agree to our information collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance to this Privacy Policy.

By clicking 'Submit' or 'I agree' during the registration process or by Your continued use of the Service following the posting of this Privacy Policy (as applicable), You agree to this Privacy Policy. This is Our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with Our Terms and Conditions and any additional applicable terms posted on Our Platforms. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy and will notify You of these changes by posting the modified terms on Our Platforms. We recommend that You revisit this Privacy Policy regularly

## 2\. Information Collected

We consider information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, first and last name, date of birth, credit card information, home or other physical address, email address, phone number or other contact information to be Personal Information ('Personal Information'). You may be asked to provide Personal Information when You use Our website, register for an account or to use the Services. The Personal Information that We collect may include information such as: contact information (including telephone number), shipping information, billing information, transaction history, website usage preferences, and feedback regarding the Services. This information is held by Us on our servers from time to time. In addition, when You interact with the Services, Our servers keep an activity log unique to You that collects certain administrative and traffic information including: source IP address, time of access, date of access, web page(s) visited, language use, software crash reports and type of browser used. This information is essential for the provision and quality of the Services. We do not collect Personal Information about You on the Services without Your knowledge.

## 3\. Information Use

We use the Personal Information We collect from You to deliver Our Services, to provide customer support, to undertake necessary security and identify verification checks, to process any of Your online transactions, meet certain business requirements and for any other purpose related to the operation of the Services. Your Personal Information may also be used by Us to provide You with promotional offers and information regarding Our product and service and in order for Us to better provide a range of services and improved customer service. From time-to-time, We may request information from You via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and, therefore, You have the choice of whether or not to disclose such information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name, correspondence address and telephone number), and demographic information (such as zip or postal code or age). By accepting any contest prize or winnings from Us, You consent to use of Your name and likeness for advertising and promotional purposes without additional compensation, except where prohibited by law. Unless You have elected not to receive promotional information, We may also use Your Personal Information (including Your email address and phone number) to provide You with information regarding Our product, service and promotions, including future gaming products.

In order to play real money games on the Service, You will be required to send money to and receive money from Us. We may use third-party electronic payment processors and/or financial institutions to process such financial transactions. By accepting this Privacy Policy, You expressly consent to Personal Information necessary for the processing of transactions being shared, including, where necessary, the transfer of information outside of Your country. We take steps to ensure that Our arrangements protect Your privacy.

We may disclose Your Personal Information if required to do so by law, or if We believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with any legal process served on Us, any of Our site or the Service or in circumstances where We are under a substantially similar legal obligation; (2) protect and defend Our rights or property; or (3) act to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public. If, in Our sole determination, You are found to have cheated or attempted to defraud Us, the Group, or any other user of the Services in any way including but not limited to game manipulation or payment fraud, or if We suspect You of fraudulent payment, including use of stolen credit cards, or any other fraudulent activity (including any chargeback or other reversal of a payment) or prohibited transaction (including money laundering), We reserve the right to share this information (together with Your identity) with other online gaming sites, banks, credit card companies, and appropriate agencies.

## 4\. Access / Opt-Out

You may 'opt out' of receiving any promotional communications either by choosing to opt out directly from your personal profile / account located on Our site or the Service or in an email You receive from Us, or at any time by sending an email to support@WinnersIsland.com. In addition, You may update manually or contact Us by email if You: 1) want to confirm the accuracy of the Personal Information We have collected about You; 2) would like to update Your Personal Information; and/or 3) have any complaint regarding Our use of Your Personal Information. If requested, We will (a) update any information You have provided to Us, provided that You provide evidence as We may reasonably require for such changes, or (b) mark any information to prohibit future use for marketing purposes. For the avoidance of doubt, nothing in this Privacy Policy shall prevent Us from retaining Your Personal Information where We are required to do so by law.

## 5\. Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are stored on Your computer or equipment when You visit certain online pages that record Your preferences. We use cookies to track use of Our site. We also may use cookies to monitor traffic to the site, improve the Services and make it easier and/or more relevant for Your use.

## 5.1 When do We use Cookies?

**5.1.1 During the registration process**

These cookies will hold information collected during Your registration and will allow Us to recognize You as a customer and provide You with the service You require. We may also use this data to better understand Your interests while online and to enhance Your visits to Our Platform.

**5.1.2 On Our Website / Platform**

For visitors to Our website, We use cookies to collect information and track Your use of the WinnersIsland website / Platform in order to provide you with more personalized user expectance and content and allow You to sign in easily and play WinnersIsland’s games quickly

Cookies allows us to:

  * Better understand Your preferences and offer You more relevant promotional offers. 
  * Identify Your preferences when customizing content or functionality for You. 
  * Confirm You are a registered user and save Your log-in details when accessing certain Services on Our website. 
  * Collect statistics on the use of Our Services. 
  * We may also use cookies and web beacons to ensure that Our mailing tools are working properly. 

## 5.2 How can I refuse or opt out of cookies?

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but, if You prefer, You can usually modify Your browser setting to decline cookies. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell You how to prevent Your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify You when You receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. If You choose to decline cookies, You may not be able to experience all of the interactive features on Our site. 

## 6\. Security

We understand the importance of information security and the techniques needed to secure information. We store all of the Personal Information We receive directly from You in a password-protected database residing within Our secure network behind active state-of-the-art firewall software. WinnersIsland uses a VeriSign Secure Socket Layer (SSL), EV Certified Version 3 with 128-bit encryption.

## 7\. International Transfers

Personal Information collected on the Service may be stored and processed in any country in which We or Our affiliates, suppliers, ESPs or agents maintain facilities. By using the Service, You expressly consent to any transfer of information outside of Your country (including to third countries that may not have been assessed as having adequate privacy laws). Nevertheless, We take steps to ensure that Our agents, affiliates and suppliers comply with Our standards of privacy regardless of their location.

## Legal Disclaimer

Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control. 

Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any account ID or password you use to register, and you should always be careful and responsible whenever disclosing information online.
